[
    {
      "question": "What is the key principle of improv when it comes to offers?",
      "answer": "Yes, and"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does it mean to 'Yes, and'?",
      "answer": "Accepting and building upon the offers/ideas of others."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Zen-like attention?",
        "answer": "The ability to stay fully present and engaged in the moment."
      },
      {
        "question": "What does it mean to 'BE OBVIOUS'?",
        "answer": "Embrace the simplest and most direct choices that come to mind in a scene"
      },
      {
        "question": "What are the key elements to establish in a scene?",
        "answer": "The who (characters), the why (motivation), and the where (setting/environment)."
      },
      {
        "question": "What does it mean to 'be the expert'?",
        "answer": "Being the expert means portraying a character who possesses deep knowledge and expertise in a specific subject/field"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the game 'What Comes Next' played in class?",
        "answer": "In 'What Comes Next', one player stands to do a scene and starts by saying 'What comes first'. The audience then gives a suggestion, and the player performs that suggestion. Afterward, the player asks 'What comes next?' and the performers act out the offers that the audience gives, one offer at a time."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is 'Category Category Category Die' ?",
        "answer": "'Category Category Category Die' is a game where players take turns naming items within a category. The goal is to keep the category going by naming items that fit the category, but if someone hesitates or repeats an item, they are out of the game and 'DIE' by the audience. The game ends if one player is left!"
      },
      {
        "question": "What are the names of the TAPS 103 instructors?",
        "answer": "The wonderful Dan Klein and Lisa Rowland and our amazing TA Daania Tahir!"
      },
      {
        "question": "How should you typically start a scene (neutral, negative, positive, etc)?",
        "answer": "It is generally recommended to start a scene in improv with a positive or neutral tone rather than immediately introducing conflict."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the importance of embracing mistakes?",
        "answer": "Embracing mistakes is crucial in improv because it allows performers to turn unexpected moments into opportunities!"
      },
      {
        "question": "Why is spontaneity important??",
        "answer": "Embracing spontaneity allows improvisers to tap into their creativity, follow their instincts, and build authentic and engaging scenes!"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the 'Shrinking Time Machine' game?",
        "answer": "In the 'Shrinking Time Machine' game, players start with a two person scene and grow and shrink in player size while adapting to a different scene each time the size changes. Each player takes turns entering the time machine and acting out a scene from a specific time period or event. As the machine shrinks, the scenes become shorter and more condensed. All performers/players are encouraged to think quickly on their feet, establishing characters, relationships, and conflicts within a limited amoutn of time."
      },
      {
        "question": "If a character is fidgeting, does this portray low-status??",
        "answer": "Yes, fidgeting is employed by performers to indicate low-status. This usually hapepns during nervous movements, such as shifting weight, fiddling with objects/body parts."
      },
      {
        "question": "What is space-object work?",
        "answer": "Space-object work refers to the technique in improv where performers use imaginary objects that hold real physical properties to use on the performance stage"
      },
      {
        "question": "Is showing up on time important?",
        "answer": "Yes, ALWAYS SHOW UP!"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the 'One Word Story' game?",
        "answer": "In the 'One-Word Story' game, players create a story one word at a time. The key parts of the game are to build upon the words contributed by others, so it is important to pay attention to what is being offered. This game exercises attention, spontaneity, and ability to create characters flow and tension of a story at a quick pace."
      },
      {
        "question": "How does getting your partners in trouble make improv more interesting?",
        "answer": "Getting your partners in trouble adds excitement and unpredictability to improv scenes. Introducing conflicts to your partners pushes both you and your partners ability to think on your feet(s) and adapt to new situations."
      },
      {
        "question": "What are some blockers to spontaneity?",
        "answer": "Overhtinking, trying to find the 'best' answer, thinking ahead, judgement, fear of failure"
      },  
      {
        "question": "What is the student-run improv club on campus called?",
        "answer": "The Simps!"
      }
  ]
  